<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>

<FlavorTextDefs
xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../../data/Schema/FlavorText.xsd">

	<FlavorTextDef>
		<InternalName>HISTORY_LEADER</InternalName>
  
		<FlavorTextOption>
			<Text>Had an identical twin that went missing years ago.</Text>
			<Text>Extensive criminal record was erased by government contacts.</Text>
			<Text>Has incurred high amounts of gambling debt.</Text>
			<Text>Incredibly vain, known to kill people more attractive than them.</Text>
			<Text>A depressed former assassin, tormented by their guilt.</Text>
			<Text>Tight-fisted with money and despised by their underlings.</Text>
			<Text>Feared and hated, but secretly desperate to be liked.</Text>
			<Text>Openly talks about their desire to retire and be done with this.</Text>
			<Text>Has recurring dreams of themselves in a past life.</Text>
			<Text>Is responsible for their father's death.</Text>
			<Text>Has a more famous sibling they despise.</Text>
			<Text>Spent their entire life chasing means of achieving immortality.</Text>
			<Text>Has an alarming number of criminal connections.</Text>
			<Text>Is a lifelong bureaucrat, committed to due process above all.</Text>
			<Text>Spent several years living under an assumed identity.</Text>
			<Text>Is distrustful of new technology, prefers the old ways.</Text>
			<Text>Was forced to watch their parents' execution.</Text>
			<PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
		</FlavorTextOption>
		
		<FlavorTextOption>
			<Requirements>
				<CitizenRace>Race_Human</CitizenRace>
			</Requirements>
			<Text>Raised by squatters in a destitute factory.</Text>
			<Text>Trained a bit as a chef, always wanted to open a restaurant.</Text>
			<Text>Formerly brain washed by religious cultists.</Text>
			<Text>Suffers from claustrophobia, hates being in spaceships.</Text>
			<Text>Has no friends or family outside of their political party.</Text>
			<Text>Failed out of medical school. Doesn't like talking about it.</Text>
			<Text>Avoided military service thanks to family connections.</Text>
			<Text>Excluded from a family inheritance and terribly bitter about it.</Text>
			<Text>Scarred in a duel with a romantic rival. They won though.</Text>
			<Text>Lost their sense of smell in an industrial accident.</Text>
			<Text>Descends from minor European nobility.</Text>
			<Text>Spent their youth in a Tibetan monastery.</Text>
			<Text>A former wharf rat, escaped from the slums of a port city.</Text>
			<Text>Had military parents, spent years moving around the solar system.</Text>
			<Text>A former sailor, used to spending months alone at sea.</Text>
			<Text>A career diplomat, who loves understanding all the details.</Text>
			<Text>Overcame a crippling drug addiction.</Text>
			<Text>Lost two toes from frostbite in a mountaineering accident.</Text>
			<Text>A former engineer, easily distracted by minute details.</Text>
			<Text>Badly burnt in a cooking accident as a child.</Text>
			<Text>Grooms themselves to look identical to a long dead friend from their childhood.</Text>
			<Text>Constantly flipping a coin of alien origin.</Text>
			<Text>Has been known to violently enforce the use of proper grammar.</Text>
			<Text>Insists the Precursors still walk among us in disguise.</Text>
			<Text>Loves to sing, but has a dreadful sense of pitch, rhythm, and harmony.</Text>
			<Text>Lost contact with their family following a long trip at relativistic speeds.</Text>
			<Text>Loves to assign humiliating pet names to their advisors.</Text>
			<Text>Has a terrible sense of humor, but doesn't know it because they're surrounded by sycophants.</Text>
			<Text>Is guided by two dueling voices in their head, whose combined advice never fails.</Text>
			<Text>Once accidentally committed an act of cannibalism.</Text>
			<Text>Meticulous and organized, undertook extensive training to be an archivist.</Text>
			<Text>Is menaced by anonymous death threats that arrive every day from some unknown entity.</Text>
			<Text>Serves at the pleasure of a secret organization who could kill them at any moment.</Text>
			<Text>Experiences synaesthesia when speaking with alien species.</Text>
			<Text>Carries the skull of their former nemesis with them.</Text>
			<Text>Spent decades under a vow of silence, communicating with no-one.</Text>
			<Text>Was trapped on a colony ship adrift for many decades.</Text>
			<Text>Diligently works every day on their autobiography.</Text>
			<Text>Has a terrible stutter, and crippling fear of public speaking.</Text>
			<Text>Was the only survivor of a training accident at a military academy.</Text>
			<Text>Is terrified of their own reflection, and has banned all mirrored surfaces from the capital.</Text>
			<Text>Trained to be a scientist but didn't have the aptitude. Secretly bitter about it.</Text>
			<Text>Encountered a space faring monster when younger, is now obsessed with finding it again.</Text>
			<Text>Swindled into dubious martial training as a youth, now has strange notions of 'honor.'</Text>
			<Text>Due to an unknown childhood incident, refuses to be in a poorly lit room or space.</Text>
			<Text>Is obsessed with genealogy, and fully convinced ancestral knowledge is real.</Text>
			<Text>Loudly insists they are the reincarnation of a great leader from ancient history.</Text>
			<Text>Possesses a mysterious artifact which prevents them from casting a shadow.</Text>
			<Text>Was raised by their parent's enemies as a hostage.</Text>
			<Text>Is the last member of an ancient bloodline.</Text>
			<Text>Is quite likely the child of prophecy who will lead their people to greatness or doom.</Text>
			<Text>Prefers verbal communication, even to the point of shredding documents, unread.</Text>
			<Text>A merciless disciplinarian, who expects perfection from their subordinates.</Text>
			<Text>Faced many accusations of having 'impure' beliefs when younger. The accusations were true.</Text>
			<Text>Was once framed for the murder of a political rival.</Text>
			<Text>Comes from a family which secretly backs space piracy.</Text>
			<Text>Has been handed everything to them on a silver platter. Never been challenged.</Text>
			<Text>A lucid dreamer, who uses their dreams to rehearse important meetings.</Text>
			<PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
		</FlavorTextOption>

		<FlavorTextOption>
			<Requirements>
				<CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_Vendetta</CitizenTrait>
			</Requirements>
			<Text>Secretly maintains a list of names, several already crossed off it.</Text>
			<PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
		</FlavorTextOption>
		<FlavorTextOption>
			<Requirements>
				<CitizenTrait>UnitTrait_Compassion</CitizenTrait>
			</Requirements>
			<Text>Is more concerned than most with the welfare of the poorest members of society.</Text>
			<PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
		</FlavorTextOption>
		<FlavorTextOption>
			<Requirements>
				<CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_ArrangedMarriage</CitizenTrait>
			</Requirements>
			<Text>Narrowly escaped an arranged marriage.</Text>
			<PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
		</FlavorTextOption>
		<FlavorTextOption>
			<Requirements>
				<CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_LostFortune</CitizenTrait>
			</Requirements>
			<Text>Has already made a fortune and lost it.</Text>
			<PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
		</FlavorTextOption>
		<FlavorTextOption>
			<Requirements>
				<CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_Scars</CitizenTrait>
			</Requirements>
			<Text>Body covered in scars they refuse to talk about.</Text>
			<PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
		</FlavorTextOption>
		<FlavorTextOption>
			<Requirements>
				<CitizenTrait>LeaderTrait_Brooch</CitizenTrait>
			</Requirements>
			<Text>Never seen without a mysterious brooch of unknown origin.</Text>
			<PreferenceWeight>11</PreferenceWeight>
		</FlavorTextOption>
		
	</FlavorTextDef>

	<FlavorTextDef>
		<InternalName>HISTORY_PLANET</InternalName>
  
		<FlavorTextOption>
			<Text>Planet Test 1</Text>
			<Text>Planet Test 2</Text>
			<Text>Planet Test 3</Text>
			<Text>Planet Test 4</Text>
			<Text>Planet Test 5</Text>
			<Text>Planet Test 6</Text>
			<Text>Planet Test 7</Text>
			<Text>Planet Test 8</Text>
			<Text>Planet Test 9</Text>
			<Text>Planet Test 10</Text>
			<PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
		</FlavorTextOption>

		<FlavorTextOption>
			<Requirements>
				<ListenerFaction>FACTION_TERRAN</ListenerFaction>
			</Requirements>
			<Text>Terran Planet Test 1</Text>
			<Text>Terran Planet Test 2</Text>
			<Text>Terran Planet Test 3</Text>
			<Text>Terran Planet Test 4</Text>
			<Text>Terran Planet Test 5</Text>
			<PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
		</FlavorTextOption>
	</FlavorTextDef>

	<FlavorTextDef>
		<InternalName>HISTORY_SHIP</InternalName>
  
		<FlavorTextOption>
			<Text>A leaking coolant system forces the ship to keep the engine compartment near freezing.</Text>
			<Text>Most crew members believe this ship is haunted.</Text>
			<Text>The crew has been running a complex holodeck simulation nonstop for years.</Text>
			<Text>Over fourteen crew members have simply disappeared since launch.</Text>
			<Text>Scan anomalies suggest that this ship is being used to ship unreported goods.</Text>
			<Text>The crew revere the captain of this ship as a messiah, and not a compassionate one.</Text>
			<Text>The death of the ships captain led the crew to recreate him in the holodeck, and this image still leads them.</Text>
			<Text>The crew is victim to unusual bouts of paranoia and delusion, though they usually pass after a few days.</Text>
			<Text>Captured stowaways forced the crew to reallocate some rooms as a makeshift prison.</Text>
			<Text>A life support failure killed the first crew a few hours after launch, the second crew is faring much better.</Text>
			<Text>This ship's cantina is renown throughout the fleet.</Text>
			<PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
		</FlavorTextOption>

		<FlavorTextOption>
			<Requirements>
				<ListenerFaction>FACTION_TERRAN</ListenerFaction>
			</Requirements>
			<Text>An annual onboard poker tournament consumes the crews attention.</Text>
			<Text>The captain has outlawed familial relations onboard, including spouses.</Text>
			<Text>There is an unusual amount of young children onboard this ship.</Text>
			<Text>A small recording crew is onboard this ship to immortalize the journey.</Text>
			<Text>The captain is a fan of Italian opera, and subjects the crew to it on a regular basis.</Text>
			<PreferenceWeight>10</PreferenceWeight>
		</FlavorTextOption>
	</FlavorTextDef>
  
</FlavorTextDefs>